gettimeblocks.com 2019-03-18

# TimeBlocks - Mobile Planner (Calendar/To-do/Memo)

  * ###### 1\. General

Day2Life Inc., (the “Company”) values the protection of personal information of the members using Time Blocks, and uses our best efforts to protect the personal information of the members.  
The Company is in compliance with all applicable laws and regulations, as well as all public announcements, ordinances and guidelines established by government authorities, regarding protection of personal information, including the Personal Information Protection Act and the Act on Promotion of Utilization of Information and Communications Network (the “Communications Network Laws”).  
This Privacy Policy applies to the members who use Time Blocks, and provides the information on the purpose and manner of using personal information provided by the members and the measures taken by the Company to protect such personal information. 

  * ###### 2\. Consent to Collection and Use of Personal Information

The Company collects the minimum amount of personal information required for the execution and performance of the service use agreement by using lawful and fair methods, and provides information to the members regarding consent to the collection and use of personal information at the time of member registration in order to collect personally identifiable personal information of the members. When a member clicks on the “agree” button, it is deemed as the member’s consent to the collection and use of his/her personal information. 

  * ###### 3\. Items of Personal Information to be Collected

    * 1\. Account information

      * User ID, password, name, age, country information and time zone are stored in order to identify members for provision of services.
    * 2\. Calendar information

      * Calendar information stored in local storage of member’s device, weekend subscription history, calendar information of third-party calendar application, and information associated with the foregoing (location, contact, date of birth and other linked data) are stored to provide the planner service of Time Blocks. 
    * 3\. Tasks and memo information

      * Tasks and memo information of third-party application stored in local storage of member’s device, and information associated with the foregoing (location, contact and other linked data) are stored to provide the planner service of Time Blocks.
    * 4\. Device information

      * Member’s device information (model name, type, operating system and version, etc.), language setting, mobile network and internet service provider, and device unique ID are stored in order to provide customized information to members.
    * 5\. Payment history

      * Paid contents purchased by members and payment history in order to check refund and payment history.
    * 6\. Usage history and log data, etc.

      * Age, gender, information on interests as customized by the member in the service, features used by members, access time, information on advertisement which a member has clicked on or saved, and other log data are stored in order to provide a better service experience.
    * 7\. Location information

      * Location information is accessed through member’s device and stored in order to provide customized information to members.
  * ###### 4\. Collection Method of Personal Information 

The Company collects personal information using the following methods:

    * 1\. Collection through voluntary provision of information by members for registration or use of the service
    * 2\. In case of members who log in using his/her Facebook ID, at his/her option, automatic collection from the relevant partner companies.
    * 3\. In case of members who have linked Time Blocks with a third party application (e.g., Evernote), at his/her option, automatic collection from the third party.
    * 4\. Collection from the local storage of the member’s device at the member’s option
    * 5\. Collection through log data collection tool. 
  * ###### 5\. Purpose for Collection and Use of Personal Information 

The Company utilizes the personal information collected for the following purposes; provided that, the Company may only dispatch for-profit advertising information to the members for whom the Company has obtained separate consent to receipt of for-profit advertising information. 

    * 1\. Membership Management

      * For user authentication of membership service, personal identification, prevention of illicit use or unauthorized use by fraudulent member, confirmation of duplicate registration, confirmation of a member's intent to join, verification of age, consent from a legal representative (parent) to collect personal information of children under 14 years of age, maintenance of records for dispute resolution, customer service including handling with complaint, and sending notification
    * 2\. Service Quality Enhancement

      * Development of new service, provision of customized service, service based on demographic characteristics, confirmation of service effectiveness, identification of access frequency, and statistics on use of service by members 
    * 3\. Marketing and Advertising

      * Provision of information on customized events, for-profit advertising information and opportunity for participating thereto. 
  * ###### 6\. Outsourcing for Processing of Collected Personal Information

The Company outsources processing of personal information to external professional entities for service enhancement as set forth below. 

    * 1\. AWS (Amazon Web Services)

      * Outsourced Task: Infrastructure management for service delivery and analysis
    * 2\. Google analytics 

      * Outsourced Task: Service availability analysis support
    * 3\. Mixpanel

      * Outsourced Task: Service availability analysis support
    * 4\. Sendgrid

      * Outsourced Task: Dispatch of newsletters 
    * 5\. Branch.io

      * Outsourced Task: Marketing performance measurement support
    * 6\. Appsflyer

      * Outsourced Task: Marketing performance measurement support
  * ###### 7\. Provision of Personal Information to Third Parties 

    * 1\. The Company does not use personal information of the members or provide it to any third parties beyond the scope specified in this Privacy Policy, except where there has been consent by a member or it falls under one of the following cases. 

      * a. Where it is necessary for charge of payment for the services
      * b. Where there is a request made by relevant authorities for the purposes of investigation, litigation or administration in accordance with the relevant laws and regulations
      * c. Where it is provided for statistics, academic research or market survey in a reprocessed format by which individuals are not identifiable.
      * d. Where there is a request in accordance with procedures prescribed by laws and regulations. 
    * 2\. In case of full or partial transfer of the Company’s business, or in case of assignment or succession of any rights or obligations of the Company due to merger or inheritance, the Company will notify the members of such fact and the method and procedure of revoking their consent in the event that he/she does not want the transfer of his/her personal information in order to protect the member’s right regarding protection of personal information. 
    * 3\. In the event that it becomes necessary to provide the personal information of the members to a third party in order to provide better service, the Company will go through the process of providing prior notice to the members of the identity of the recipient of the personal information, items of personal information to be provided, purpose of use of information to be provided, how long the personal information would be shared and how they will be protected and managed, and seek consent from the members. Unless consented by the member, information will not be provided to third parties. 
  * ###### 8\. Period of Retention and Use of Personal Information 

    * 1\. When the purpose of collecting or receiving personal information is achieved, the personal information of the members will be destroyed. In case a member receives disposition of deletion of membership ID due to membership withdrawal or fraudulent entry of personal information, the collected personal information will be permanently deleted and will be processed so that it may not be used for any purpose. Nonetheless, because there is a possibility of damage arising from unwanted membership withdrawal due to identity theft, the Company will temporarily retain personal information for 7-day grace period after application for withdrawal, and such will be notified to the member upon termination/cancellation of service. After 7 days, the personal information will be permanently deleted from the Company’s membership information database. 
    * 2\. While the personal information of the members are destroyed without delay after achievement of the purpose of collection and use of the personal information, the Company may retain the personal information in the following cases for the specified period, and will not use it for any other purpose. 

      * a. Fraudulent use history: 1 year 
      * b. Record regarding contract or withdrawal of subscription: 5 years
      * c. Record on payment and supply of goods: 5 years
      * d. Record on customer complaint or dispute resolution: 3 years
      * e. Record on display/advertisement: 6 months
      * f. Visit history to web and application: 1 year 
  * ###### 9\. Procedure and Method of Destruction of Personal Information

After achievement of the purpose of use of collected personal information, the personal information is moved to a separate database and destroyed in accordance with the applicable retention period and usage period without delay. The procedure and method of destruction is as follows.

    * 1\. Destruction Procedure 

      * After achieving its purpose, the personal information provided by a member for service registration is deleted or destroyed after being retained for a set period of time depending on the cause for protection of information (please refer to Period of Retention and Use) pursuant to the internal policy and other relevant laws and regulations. 
    * 2\. Destruction Method

      * Personal information written or printed on paper are destroyed by crush in a grinder, while personal information stored in an electronic file form are deleted by technical method which makes it impossible to reproduce the record. 
  * ###### 10\. Rights of Member and Legal Representative and Method of Exercising Rights 

    * 1\. Members and their legal representatives may view and modify their own registered personal information or that of their children under the age of 14 at any time, and may request for unsubscribing of their memberships. 
    * 2\. In order to view or modify the personal information of the members or children under the age of 14, the members and their legal representatives may directly view, modify or withdraw after a personal identification procedure by clicking on ‘Update Profile’ (or ‘Edit Profile’, etc.) for modification or ‘Delete My Account’ for withdrawal (revocation of consent). Alternatively, please contact the Privacy Officer by writing, phone or e-mail, and then we will take the necessary steps without delay. 
    * 3\. When a member requests a correction of personal information due to an error, his/her personal information will not be used or provided until the correction is completed. In addition, when the erroneous personal information has already been provided to third parties, the results of the correction process will be notified to the third parties without delay so that appropriate correction can be made. 
    * 4\. The Company ensures that any personal information that is terminated or deleted at the request of a member or his/her legal representatives is processed in accordance with “8. Period of Retention and Use of Personal Information” and that it may not be viewed or used for any other purpose. 
  * ###### 11\. Member’s Obligations

Members shall accurately enter the most recent personal information in order to prevent any unexpected accident. Members shall be liable for any accidents arising from any inaccurate information entered by him/her. If a member enters any fraudulent information or personal information of others, his/her use of the account may be restricted.  
Members using the Company’s service have the right to the protection of their personal information, as well as the obligation to protect themselves and not to infringe upon others’ information. Members shall be careful not to reveal their personal information, including their ID and password, and shall use caution not to damage personal information of others, including postings. If a member fails to perform such obligation and damages others’ information or dignity, he/she may be subject to punishment under the Communications Network Laws. 

  * ###### 12\. Technical and Administrative Measures for Personal Information 

In handling members’ personal information, the Company takes technical/administrative measures as follows not to cause the loss, theft, leakage or alteration of, or damage to, personal information.

    * 1\. Anti-Hacking Measures

      * The Company strives to prevent leakage of or damage to members’ personal information caused by hacking or virus. The Company tries to prevent leakage of or damage to members’ personal information or materials, and uses encoded communications for safe transmission of personal information through networks. The Company operates the intrusion prevention system to block unauthorized access from outside. 
    * 2\. Minimization of Persons Handling with Personal Information and Training 

      * The Company limits the number of employees who handle with personal information, and regularly updates the separate password provided for handling of personal information. The Company always emphasizes the importance of observing the Privacy Policy through training sessions carried out for employees from time to time. 
    * 3\. Operation of Dedicated Personal Information Protection Team

      * The Company, through internal team dedicated to personal information protection, checks to see whether the Private Policy is complied with by employees and strives to find immediately solutions to problems, if any. However, the Company shall not be responsible for any issues caused by leakage of ID, password and the like due to members’ carelessness or any reason which is not a willful misconduct or gross negligence of the Company.
  * ###### 13\. Duty to Notify

In the event that there are any additions, deletions, or modifications made to the current version of the Privacy Policy, the Company will provide notice thereof on the website of Time Blocks (http://gettimeblocks.com) or through the “Notification” within the service not less than 30 days prior to the effective date of such change. 

  * ###### 14\. Installation and Operation of Automatic Collection System of Personal Information and Related Matters about Refusal

    * 1\. Collection of Cookie

      * The Company uses ‘cookies’ that frequently save and retrieve a member’s information in order to provide personalized and customized services. A cookie is a very small text file that the server, used to operate the Company’s website, sends to a member’s browser. It is saved in the hard disk of the member’s computer. After it is saved, the website server reads the cookie saved on the member’s hard disk when the member visits the website in order to maintain the configurations of the member and provide customized services. A cookie does not automatically collect information that can identify members, and members can refuse to save cookies or delete the saved cookies at all times.
    * 2\. Installation/Operation of Cookie and Refusal

      * Members reserve the right to choose whether to install cookies. Thus, members can allow saving of all cookies, check a cookie each time it is saved, or refuse to save cookies all together by selecting an option on the web browser. However, if a member refuses to save cookies, he/she might experience difficulties in use of certain services, such as individualized and customized services, etc.  
\- Setting Method  
Internet Explorer: Click the [Tools] > [Internet Option] > [Privacy Tab] > Adjust setting under [Level of Private Information Processing] 
  * ###### 15\. Supervisor and Responsible Person in Charge of Management of Personal Information

The Company considers personal information of the members very valuably and does its best to prevent any damage to, or infringement or leakage of, personal information of members. If you have any complaints in regard to personal information while using the service, please report it to the Personal Information Management Officer or Personal Information Protection Officer and we will respond to you right away.

    * 1\. Personal Information Management Officer 

      * Name : Wonil Park
      * Position : Representative Director
      * E-mail address: contact@gettimeblocks.com
    * 2\. Personal Information Protection Officer

      * Name: Jongyi Kim
      * Position: Research and Development Team
      * E-mail address: contact@gettimeblocks.com
